A Guide to Records of the Secretary of Finance, 1998-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Secretary of Finance, 1998-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
The Library of Virginia
44698
40.7 cu. ft. (42 boxes)
Virginia Secretary of Transportation
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78, 2.2-3800, and 2.2-3705.1-8. Restricted documents have been sealed within the collection.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by Governor Tim Kaine on Jan. 14, 2010.
Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties, compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governors top management team or "secretariats," as they are called now. The General Assembly in 1972 created six Secretariats positions initially. As government reorganized, that number fluctuated when government agencies expanded or consolidated.
Since the establishment of a secretarial system in 1972, there have been several reorganizations of that system. The financial management function of the state has shifted from under the direction of the Secretary of Finance to the Secretary of Administration; then to Secretary of Administration and Finance and currently back to the Secretary of Finance, through various reorganizations of state government from 1970's to the present. The function of the secretary is to provide sound fiscal management and recommend to the Governor a comprehensive budget for those agencies under his jurisdiction. The secretary's responsibilities are: to monitor programs, services and performance of subordinate state agencies to develop state policies programs for long-range planning and policy formulation; and approve solicitation or acceptance of any donations, gifts or grants; to hold agency heads accountable for their agency's administrative, fiscal and program performance. All secretaries are appointed by the governor and serve at his will.
Scope and Content
Records of the Secretary of Finance, 2006-2010, during the administration of Governor Timothy Kaine. The collection is housed in 42 boxes and includes agendas, briefings, brochures, clippings, contracts, correspondence, financial statements, itineraries, maps, memorandum, newsletters, notes, photographs, programs, publications, reports, and other documents. The collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Contents List
- Constituent Mail and Correspondence, Jan. 2006-Jan. 2007. (Box 1)
- Constituent Mail and Correspondence, Jan. 2007-Aug. 2007. (Box 2)
- Constituent Mail and Correspondence, Sep. 2007-Nov. 2007. (Box 3)
- VIP - FYI, FYI Reassignments, 2007. (Box 3)
- Reports Sent to Secretary of Finance, 2007. (Box 3)
- Budget Requests 2008-2010 Biennial Budget, 2008. (Box 3)
- Legislative Files, Session House and Senate Bills, 2007. (Box 4)
- Legislative Files, 2006-2007. (Box 5)
- Legislative Files, 1998-2006. (Box 6)
- Legislative Files - House Bills, 2006. (Box 7)
- Legislative Files - Senate Bills, 2006-2007. (Box 8)
- Legislative Files-Proposed Legislation of the Finance Secretariat, 2006. (Box 9)
- General Assembly Study Reports, 2006 (Box 9)
- House Bills, 01-1699, 2006. (Box 9)
- Senate Bills, 1-899, 2006. (Box 9)
- Non-State Agency Budget Requests for 2008-2010. (Box 10)
- 2008 Session LAS Notebook, House Bills 1-1599, 2008. (Box 10)
- 2008 Session LAS Notebook, Senate Bills 1-799, 2008. (Box 10)
- 2008 Session EBR/FIS Notebook Senate Bills 1-399, 2008. (Box 10)
- 2008 Session EBR/FIS Notebook Senate Bills 400-799, 2008. (Box 10)
- 2008 Session EBR/FIS Notebook, Hosue Bills 1-799 - Secretary of Finance, 2008. (Box 10)
- Legislative Files, SB700-1399, 2008. (Box 11)
- Legislative Files, HB1600-3099, 2008. (Box 11)
- Legislative Files, 2006. (Box 11)
- Legislative Proposals, DPB-Tax-Treasury, 2006. (Box 11)
- HB3202 Industry Advisory Group, 2007. (Box 12)
- Capital Project Approvals, 2007. (Box 12)
- Budget-Transportation, 2006. (Box 12)
- Update: the newsletter of the Virginia Municipal League Oct. 2006. (Box 12)
- Tran[sportation] HB3202, 2007. (Box 12)
- Republican Legislators Detail Transportation Compromise and Reform Funding Plan, 2007. (Box 12)
- Republican Transportation Plan, 2007. (Box 12)
- Alternative for a tranportation compromise, n.d. (Box 12)
- Transportation, 2006-2007. (Box 12)
- Transportation/Jefferson Institute, 2004-2006 (Box 12)
- Transportation, 2006-2007. (Box 12)
- PRTC, 2006-2007. (Box 12)
- NVTA MOU, 2007. (Box 12)
- Goldmans Sachs-Discussion Materials, 2006. (Box 12)
- Transportation-HB3202, 2007. (Box 12)
- NVTA Bond Validation, 2007. (Box 12)
- Port City Reimbursement (Tran), 2007.
- Trans. HB3202, 2002-2007. (Box 12)
- Trans.-CSX, 2007. (Box 12)
- I-495 PPTA Agreement Business Terms, 2007. (Box 12)
- Transportation Plan, 2005-2006. (Box 12)
- Pocahontas Parkway Agreement, 2006. (Box 12)
- Trans. Dulles Road, 2005. (Box 12)
- Potomac and Rappahannock Transportation Commission, 2007. (Box 12)
- Conference Call re: HB3202, May 2007. (Box 12)
- HB 3202, 2007. (Box 12)
- HB 3202 - Trans., 2007. (Box 12)
- Trans. HB 3202, 2007. (Box 12)
- Constituent Mail, Jan. 2009-Oct. 2009. (Box 13)
- Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, Jan. 2008-Dec. 2008. (Box 14)
- Reports to SOF, 2008. (Box 14)
- Reports/FYI, 2008. (Box 14)
- Chronological Letters, 2002. (Box 15)
- Chronological Letters, 2003. (Box 15)
- Non-State Agency Matching Fund, 2005. (Box 15)
- Chronological File, 2005. (Box 15)
- Jody M. Wagner Correspondence, 2007. (Box 16)
- Jody Wagner Constituent Mail, 2006-2008. (Box 16)
- VIP Letters, Jody Wagner, 2006-2008. (Box 16)
- State Police Oxycontin Settlement, 2007. (Box 16)
- Joint Meeting of the House Appropriations, House Finance and Senate Finance Committees, 2008. (Box 16)
- WV Bill Draft, 2008. (Box 16)
- Budget, 2008. (Box 16)
- Unfunded Mandates, 2005-2006. (Box 16)
- Joint Subcommittee for Studying Local Incentives to Private Businesses for Economic Development, 2008. (Box 16)
- Agency SWAM, 2007. (Box 16)
- SOF Strategic Plan, n.d. (Box 16)
- Wall Street Journal, 2006-2007. (Box 16)
- Queen's Visit SOF, 2007. (Box 16)
- Exec. Order 44, 2007. (Box 16)
- Energy Efficiency, 2007. (Box 16)
- Correspondence-Jody M. Wagner, 2006. (Box 16)
- PPEA, 2005. (Box 16)
- PPTA, 2005. (Box 16)
- PPEFIA Act. Guidlines Meeting, 2005. (Box 16)
- Gov's Letters-No Actions, 2006. (Box 16)
- Virginian-Pilot Article on Jody M. Wagner, 2006. (Box 16)
- Executive Orders, 2006. (Box 16)
- VEAP, 2006. (Box 16)
- Public-Private Partnerships, 2005-2006. (Box 16)
- PPEA, 2005-2006. (Box 16)
- New Jersey Phase 1 Report - Public-Private Partnership, 2006. (Box 16)
- Prayer Breakfast, 2006. (Box 16)
- SOF-Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2006. (Box 16)
- Agency Head Meeting, Feb. 2006. (Box 16)
- Agency Head Meetings, 2006-2007. (Box 16)
- VEI Summer Programs, 2006. (Box 16)
- Agency Head Meeting, May 2007. (Box 16)
- Commissioner of Revenue, 2006. (Box 16)
- Treasurers Association, 2006. (Box 16)
- Constituent Mail, Oct. 2009-Jan. 2010. (Box 17)
- Constituent Calls etc., 2006-2007. (Box 17)
- Mailed Letters (JMW), 2006-2008. (Box 17)
- LAS/EBR, 2009 Session. (Box 17)
- Agency Legislative Proposals, 2009. (Box 17)
- Budget Requests, 2009 Session. (Box 17)
- Legislative Review (LAS/EBR), 2008. (Box 17)
- Legislative Review (LAS/EBR), 2009. (Box 17)
- Legislative Instructions, 2008 Session. (Box 17)
- SOF Legislation, 2008. (Box 17)
- SOF Legislation, 2007. (Box 17)
- GA-Info re: LAS/EBR, 2006. (Box 17)
- Budget Requests, 2006. (Box 17)
- Additional Information re: Budget Requests/Meetings, 2006. (Box 17)
- Legislative Proposals, 2008. (Box 17)
- Joint Money Committee, Dec. 2006. (Box 18)
- HB 439, 2006. (Box 18)
- HB 566, 2006. (Box 18)
- HB 1052, 2006. (Box 18)
- SB 541 Substitute, 2006. (Box 18)
- HB/SB 5019 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget Overview, 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget Conferees, 2007. (Box 18)
- Budget Process, 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget, 2007. (Box 18)
- Revenue Shortfall, 2007. (Box 18)
- Revenue Stabilization Fund, 2007. (Box 18)
- The Six-Year Financial Plan, FY 2006 to 2012. (Box 18)
- Budget Letters, 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget-Misc., 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget Concerns, 2007. (Box 18)
- Differences Between House/Senate Budget Proposals, 2006. (Box 18)
- Legislative Request Form, n.d. (Box 18)
- Budget, 2008. (Box 18)
- Budget Requests, FY07-08. (Box 18)
- Rebenchmarking, 2008-2010. (Box 18)
- Budget Guidance Memo, 2007. (Box 18)
- Budget Shortfalls, 2007. (Box 18)
- Perf. Budget Meetings, 2007. (Box 18)
- Cabinet/Agency Budget Meetings, 2007. (Box 18)
- Consolidation of Support Functions and Small Agencies, 2003. (Box 18)
- Budget Issues, 2007. (Box 18)
- Biennial Budget Development, 2007. (Box 18)
- Budget Correspondence, 2007. (Box 18)
- Money Committee Letter, Sep. 2007. (Box 18)
- Appropriation Letter, Oct. 2007. (Box 18)
- Budget Documents, 2008. (Box 18)
- Agency Reduction Strategies (Governor's Comments), 2008-2010. (Box 18)
- Meeting re: HB3202, Nov. 2007. (Box 18)
- Budget Letter to Budget Conferees, Mar. 2006. (Box 18)
- Conferees Letter, Feb. 2007. (Box 18)
- Budget Amendments, 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget Action Report, Feb. 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget Amendment HB5002, 2006. (Box 18)
- Revenue Stab. Fund, 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget VETOs, 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget-Executive Amendments Session I, 2006. (Box 18)
- Requested Budget Amendments, 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 18)
- Requested Budget Amendments, 2006. (Box 18)
- Virginia Economic Bridge, 2005. (Box 18)
- Proclamation, Special Session 2006. (Box 18)
- Budget Talking Points-Conferees, 2006 (Box 18)
- Governor's Letters-Chrono., 2006. (Box 18)
- Caboose Bill, HB 5012, 2006. (Box 18)
- Joint Money Committee-Gov. Speech and SOF Report, Aug. 2006. (Box 18)
- House Bill 1650 Letter, Mar. 2007. (Box 18)
- Telework Opp. (HJR144), Jul. 2006. (Box 19)
- NASBO, 2006. (Box 19)
- Council on Virginia's Future, 2007. (Box 19)
- COVE, 2007. (Box 19)
- Sorenson-Women in Politics, 2006. (Box 19)
- VGFOA (VA Gov. Finance Officers Assoc.), 2006. (Box 19)
- Workforce Services, 2006. (Box 19)
- CSG, 2006. (Box 19)
- Norfolk Foundation, 2007. (Box 19)
- SOF-Admin., 2007. (Box 19)
- Office Supplies, 2007. (Box 19)
- SOF-Admin., 2006. (Box 19)
- VEI/CMI, 2006-2007. (Box 19)
- Constituent-Robert Gibson, 2006. (Box 19)
- Warner/Bennett Archiving, n.d. (Box 19)
- Finance Meetings and Presentations, 2006-2008. (Box 19)
- SWAM Meeting, 2008. (Box 19)
- Virginia Economic Development Partnership Presentations, 2008. (Box 19)
- Finance Presentations, 2008. (Box 19)
- Comprehensive Services Act (CSA), 2006-2007. (Box 19)
- DPB-Six-Year Plan - Update for GF 07-2012, 2006. (Box 19)
- Sub-Cabinet Community Investment, n.d. (Box 19)
- Finance Accomplishments, 2007. (Box 19)
- Higher Ed. Base Adequacy, 2007. (Box 19)
- JLARC-Licensed Psych. Services, 2007. (Box 19)
- Carryforward, 2007. (Box 19)
- WM Management Agreement, 2007. (Box 19)
- JMW Money Committee, Oct. 2007. (Box 19)
- HAC (Governor's Budget Reductions), Oct. 2007. (Box 19)
- VEAP Update, Oct. 2007. (Box 19)
- Agency Reductions, 2008-2010. (Box 19)
- Status 2002 Bond Project, 2007. (Box 19)
- Blue Ribbon Strike Force/Wilder Commission, 2007. (Box 19)
- TransTech Pharma-Economic Development Project, 2007. (Box 19)
- CMA, 2008. (Box 19)
- VA GF Revenue Forecasting Process, 2006. (Box 19)
- OPEB, 2006. (Box 19)
- Transportation, 2005. (Box 19)
- Education, 2005. (Box 19)
- VITA, 2005. (Box 19)
- PPTA Project, 2005. (Box 19)
- FOIA-Davenshi Patel, 2006. (Box 19)
- FOIA-Antonio J. Saunders, 2006. (Box 19)
- FOIA-Rodakankis Letter, 2006. (Box 19)
- VA Pilot FOIA, Sep. 2009. (Box 19)
- Amanda Hurley FOIA, 2009. (Box 19)
- Correspondence and Inquiries, 2006. (Box 19)
- Public Notice Law, 2006. (Box 19)
- VEAP, 2008. (Box 19)
- VERAS/VEAP, 2008. (Box 19)
- APA Audit, 2005. (Box 19)
- Audit Issue, 2007. (Box 19)
- Audit Responses, 2006. (Box 19)
- Management Scorecard Meeting, 2007. (Box 19)
- Tobacco Indemnifiction and Community Revitalization Endowment, 2006. (Box 19)
- Attended Events, 2007-2008. (Box 19)
- Treasury, 2008. (Box 19)
- Overview of School Efficiency Review Program. (Box 20)
- Fiscal Impact Statements, 2006. (Box 20)
- Virginia First Cities Coalition. (Box 20)
- Amendments/HB and SB. (Box 20)
- Re-Engineering. (Box 20)
- House Transportation Plan. (Box 20)
- Oil Excise Tax. (Box 20)
- BRAC Funding. (Box 20)
- Amend. HB30, Item 403. (Box 20)
- Amend HB30, Revenues. (Box 20)
- State Titling Tax (CCH). (Box 20)
- Insurance Premiums. (Box 20)
- Motor Fuel. (Box 20)
- Transportation Alternative, 2004-2006. (Box 20)
- Transportation Information, Issues, Tax. (Box 20)
- Budget-Law. (Box 20)
- Lucite Blocks. (Box 20)
- HB30 Memo. (Box 20)
- OCED Staffing. (Box 20)
- University of Mary Washington, 2008. (Box 20)
- Virginia Voluntary Accounts. (Box 20)
- Correspondence, etc., 2008. (Box 20)
- Agency Head Meetings, 2007. (Box 20)
- NGF Interest Analyses, 2007. (Box 20)
- TAX-SWaM Report, 3rd Quarter, FY07. (Box 20)
- Land Preservation Tax Credit. (Box 20)
- Tax Global Insight Summaries. (Box 20)
- Department of Planning and Budget. (Box 20)
- Six Year GF Finance Plan, Aug. 2007. (Box 20)
- Kentucky Dept. of Revenue v. Davis. (Box 20)
- Charts-Adults With Postsecondary Degree. (Box 20)
- Auditing Standards. (Box 20)
- Gov.'s Briefing-State Police's Oxycontin Settlement. (Box 20)
- Revenue Forecasting Review, 2006. (Box 20)
- Performance Data. (Box 20)
- Meeting Notes, 2006. (Box 20)
- Meeting, Dec. 2006. (Box 20)
- JLARC Letter. (Box 20)
- Meetings and Presentations, 2006. (Box 20)
- Refunds, 2007. (Box 20)
- Budget Reduction, 2008. (Box 20)
- Economic Impact-Proposed Education Investment. (Box 20)
- Ambulance Issue, 2008. (Box 20)
- FY 2007. (Box 20)
- CVCC Fees, 2008. (Box 20)
- Legislative Report, 2006. (Box 20)
- Executive Order #69, 2008. (Box 20)
- VA Lottery Report, May 2008. (Box 20)
- Budget and Funding, 2006. (Box 20)
- VPSA Report. (Box 20)
- Budget and Fees, 2006-2007. (Box 20)
- Agency Strategic Plan and Performance Measures. (Box 20)
- Loudoun County Formal Review. (Box 20)
- Commissioner's Advisory Group Meeting, June 2008. (Box 20)
- Tax Comm. Advisory Group, Mar. 2008. (Box 20)
- Tax Commissioner's Leadership Meeting. (Box 20)
- Goldman Sach's Strategic Asset Management, Dec. 2006. (Box 20)
- Goldman Sach's Strategic Asset Management, Sep. 2006. (Box 20)
- Goldman Sachs Presentation Regarding the Virginia Lottery, May 2008. (Box 20)
- Infrastructure Public-Private Partnerships, UBS, 2007. (Box 20)
- DPB-Employee Info. (Box 20)
- Tax. (Box 20)
- Virginia Retirement System Annual Report, 2007. (Box 20)
- Executive Women's Network. (Box 20)
- Attorney General. (Box 21)
- Ballard. (Box 21)
- Budget. (Box 21)
- SOF-Budget Reductions. (Box 21)
- Charlotte County. (Box 21)
- DARPA. (Box 21)
- Executive Order 57. (Box 21)
- Executive Order-Productivity and Efficiency. (Box 21)
- Fort Monroe Grants. (Box 21)
- GO Bond. (Box 21)
- Bond Bill. (Box 21)
- GPP. (Box 21)
- GMU Research Laboratory Proposed Budget Amendment. (Box 21)
- Global Scale Ratings. (Box 21)
- Hampton Tax Issue. (Box 21)
- HB 30 to House of Del. 1/2% Budget. (Box 21)
- Final Talking Points HB/SB 30. (Box 21)
- Higher Ed. Bond. (Box 21)
- Bond Bill. (Box 21)
- Budget Conferees. (Box 21)
- Higher Ed. Certification Results. (Box 21)
- Higher Ed. Certification. (Box 21)
- Level III Performance Measures. (Box 21)
- Economic Dev. ABC Corps. (Box 21)
- VITA Service Rates. (Box 21)
- Policy. (Box 21)
- Tobacco Secur., 2005. (Box 21)
- Virginia Biotech Research. (Box 21)
- Medicaid Management Information Systems Procurement. (Box 21)
- Notes. (Box 21)
- Non State. (Box 21)
- Massey Center. (Box 21)
- Letter to Sen. Stosch. (Box 21)
- Orbital. (Box 21)
- PATH Application. (Box 21)
- Productivity Measures. (Box 21)
- For Review - Pre-Payments, Don Darr. (Box 21)
- Executive Order Sustainable Community Investment. (Box 21)
- Vita and Oracle Meeting, May 2008. (Box 21)
- Fort Monroe Study and Press Release. (Box 21)
- Goldman Sachs Meeting. (Box 21)
- Restructuring Briefing to the Governor. (Box 21)
- Restructuring Government. (Box 21)
- The Virginia Center on Aging Legislative Breakfast, Jan. 2008. (Box 21)
- Sorenson. (Box 21)
- Del. Landes and Lohr SRI Letters. (Box 21)
- SRI. (Box 21)
- SRI Study and PowerPoint. (Box 21)
- SRI. (Box 21)
- SWAM. (Box 21)
- Syd Dorsey Report Friday. (Box 21)
- Syd Dorsey. (Box 21)
- RBS Infrastructure Finance and Advisory Discussion, Mar. 2008. (Box 21)
- PRTC, 2007. (Box 21)
- Robert Johnson Letter (From Cathy Ghidotti). (Box 21)
- Royal Bank of Scotland. (Box 21)
- Tuition Moderation Incentive Fund. (Box 21)
- Tran-NVTA. (Box 21)
- Transportation 2pm in Suzette's Office. (Box 21)
- Revenue Stabilization. (Box 21)
- VASCIC Virginia Advanced Shipbuilding. (Box 21)
- VCCS. (Box 21)
- VEC. (Box 21)
- VEI. (Box 21)
- Voluntary Accounts Conference Call, Apr. 2008. (Box 21)
- VML. (Box 21)
- Virginia Manufacturing. (Box 21)
- Virginia Tech Settlement. (Box 21)
- Tax Audit Management System Upgrade. (Box 22)
- Department of Taxation, 2007 Session. (Box 22)
- Accelerated Sales Tax. (Box 22)
- Department of Taxation-Business Taxation-Interaction With Local Gov. (Box 22)
- Bus. Activity Tax. (Box 22)
- Department of Taxation-Car Tax. (Box 22)
- Department of Taxation-Car Tax Relief. (Box 22)
- Department of Taxation-Commissioners of Revenue. (Box 22)
- Department of Taxation-Confidential Tax Agreement Signed by SOF. (Box 22)
- Department of Taxation-Correspondence, 2006. (Box 22)
- Agency Strategic Plan-Department of Taxation. (Box 22)
- TRS-Federal Credit Unions. (Box 22)
- TRS-Countrywide. (Box 22)
- TRS. (Box 22)
- TRS-Conf.-UCP. (Box 22)
- VRE Issue, 2007. (Box 22)
- S and P State Spending. (Box 22)
- HB 3181-Escheat Bill. (Box 22)
- Go Bond/S and P Article. (Box 22)
- DOA-Vita Issue. (Box 22)
- Treasury Correspondence. (Box 22)
- Treasury Board Can. (Box 22)
- Treasury-Virginia College Building Authority. (Box 22)
- Treasury-Virginia Public School Authority. (Box 22)
- VA Public Building Auth. (Box 22)
- Treasury-Miscellaneous. (Box 22)
- News Clips. (Box 22)
- Trs.-Presentation House Finance Committee. (Box 22)
- Tobacco Settlement Financing Corp. Audited Financial Statements. (Box 22)
- Treasury-Resumes. (Box 22)
- Treasurey-Resumes-CMI Position. (Box 22)
- Agency Strategic Plan. (Box 22)
- Horse Center-Gov's Letter with Executed Agreement. (Box 22)
- VA Horse Center. (Box 22)
- Proposed Plan to Implement Item 87(A) of Chapter 3, Acts of Assembly 2006 Special Sesson 1. (Box 22)
- Virginia Horse Center (Box 22)
- Horse Center. (Box 22)
- Gov's Working Group-Early Child. Initiatives. (Box 23)
- United Way Foundation. (Box 23)
- Fremont Investment and Loan/Wilshire Credit Corp. (Box 23)
- State Fair of Virginia. (Box 23)
- Correspondence, 2006. (Box 23)
- Taxes, 2006. (Box 23)
- SB 675 Amendment Form. (Box 23)
- Judeo-Christian Outreach Center. (Box 23)
- VITA-Creating Agile Government. (Box 23)
- HB 110-Aging. (Box 23)
- Operational Reviews - Fleet. (Box 23)
- Oper. Rev. - Receivables. (Box 23)
- Oper. Rev. - Energy. (Box 23)
- Invoices. (Box 23)
- Richmond and Lynchburg CSO Control Programs. (Box 23)
- Transportation. (Box 23)
- Chesapeake Bay Agreement. (Box 23)
- Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel. (Box 23)
- Transportation Revenues. (Box 23)
- Sustainable Rev. Increases. (Box 23)
- Press Release Trans. (Box 23)
- Ins. Premium Tax. (Box 23)
- Side by Side Trans. (Box 23)
- Stats/Figures. (Box 23)
- New/Used Car Sales. (Box 23)
- Comb. SB708 Analysis. (Box 23)
- Talking Points Trans. (Box 23)
- SP - AAA Rating Article. (Box 23)
- Management Scorecard Review. (Box 23)
- Virginia BioTechnology Research Park. (Box 23)
- Russell County-SW Tech Center. (Box 23)
- Letter to Callahan, Chichester, June 2006. (Box 23)
- Rainy Day Fund. (Box 23)
- Virginia Association of Realtors. (Box 23)
- Central Virginia Food Bank. (Box 23)
- JLARC, Aug. 2006. (Box 23)
- Community Sub-Cabinet. (Box 23)
- SWAM. (Box 23)
- VA Women and Politics Conf. Schedule. (Box 23)
- Trans.-Referendum Debt, 2002. (Box 23)
- Fiscal Survey of States, June 2006. (Box 23)
- US Credit Scorecard. (Box 23)
- Editorial Board Contacts. (Box 23)
- TRS. (Box 23)
- SOA. (Box 23)
- DHRM. (Box 23)
- Agriculture. (Box 23)
- SOC. (Box 23)
- C and T. (Box 23)
- VHDA. (Box 23)
- Bond Allocation. (Box 23)
- VEDP. (Box 23)
- NPPF w/ VSBFA. (Box 23)
- VEC. (Box 23)
- Education. (Box 23)
- VA College Savings Plan. (Box 23)
- Universities-Comparison of President's Proposal vs Governor's. (Box 23)
- George Mason. (Box 23)
- ODU. (Box 23)
- Radford. (Box 23)
- Health. (Box 23)
- HHR-McKinsey Presentation, May 2007. (Box 23)
- Medicare/Medicaid Services. (Box 23)
- DMAS. (Box 23)
- VHDA. (Box 23)
- NR. (Box 23)
- Non-PT Source-BNPs. (Box 23)
- Water/Soil Meeting. (Box 23)
- PS. (Box 23)
- Virginia Beach Jail Annex. (Box 23)
- Gov.-Military. (Box 23)
- STARS. (Box 23)
- Southside Regional Jail. (Box 23)
- State Police. (Box 23)
- Dept. of Accounts End of Quarter Report, Mar. 2006. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts End of Quarter Report, June 2006. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts End of Quarter Report, Dec. 2005. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts End of Quarter Report, Mar. 2005 (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts 10-Page Report/Revenue. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Year-End Closing, 2006. (Box 24)
- DOA Relocation Policy. (Box 24)
- Report on Audit for 2005 and 2006. (Box 24)
- HR 1023. (Box 24)
- DOA Drivers Fees. (Box 24)
- DOA-FY07 Preliminary Report-General Fund. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Hotline/Fraud. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Hotline/Fraud, Executive Order 12, 2006. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Agency Risk Management and Internal Control Standards. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Schedule of CARS Closing. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Correspondence. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: General Fund Preliminary (Unaudited) Annual Report, 2006. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Monthly Cash and Investments, 2007. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Monthly Cash and Investments, 2006. (Box 24)
- OPEB Tools for Localities. (Box 24)
- DOA/Post-Employment Benefits. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Preliminary Rev. Report, FY2006. (Box 24)
- GASB 45/OPED. (Box 24)
- Dept. of Accounts: Miscellaneous. (Box 24)
- Virginia Retirement System. (Box 24)
- Lottery. (Box 24)
- VA Lottery Forecast, 2008-2010. (Box 24)
- HB 1650. (Box 24)
- DPB-Correspondence-Misc. (Box 24)
- BD Profiles-DPB. (Box 24)
- DPB Records Retention. (Box 24)
- DPB-Letter Del. Ware HB 2562. (Box 24)
- Debt Collection Recovery Fund. (Box 24)
- DPB Budget Update, 2007. (Box 24)
- Medicare Part D Trans. (Box 24)
- Annual Oil Overcharge, FY05-06. (Box 24)
- Va. Planning/Budget System. (Box 24)
- Non-State Agencies. (Box 24)
- Agency Strategic Plan. (Box 24)
- SOF-Strategic Plan. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Consolidating Tax Collection. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Debt Collection. (Box 24)
- Tax Disaster Recovery. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Earned Income Tax Credit. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Virginia Economic Forecast. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Virginia Estate Tax Act. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Federal Contractor Sales and Use Tax Pilot Audit Program. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Health Insurance Tax Credit. (Box 24)
- Tax-Va. Housing Market Comm. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Interest Rate Changes, 2006-2008. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Land Preservation Tax Credits. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Miscellaneous. (Box 24)
- Tax-Organization Structure. (Box 24)
- VA Tax Partnership Project. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Real Estate Tax. (Box 24)